

MUHAMMAD AWAIS AJMAL

Unity Game Developer

+923039269518 **awaisajam02@gmail.com**

PORTFOLIO

LINKEDIN

Bahawalpur,Punjab

EDUCATION

MS Computer Science IUB Bahawalpur 2020 - 2022

BS Computer Science **IUB Bahawalpur** 2016 - 2020

DAE Civil Technology GCT Bahawalpur 2013 - 2016

PROJECTS

- Car Driving School Games Sim
- Real World T20 Cricket 2024
- Supermarket Simulator
- Angry My Neighbor
- Scary Grandpa House
- House Makeover Cleaning
- Forest Wild Werewolf
- Offroad Bus Simulator
- Antistress Satisfying Games

LANGUAGE

- English
- Urdu

INTRESTS

- Research
- Play Video Games
- Hiking
- Education

PROFILE

In my 3 years as a Unity game developer, I've mastered diverse genres, excelled in teamwork, honed my skills in gameplay, UI, performance, and monetization, and learned the importance of timely, high-quality delivery. Ready for more challenges ahead!t.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Five River Solutions 11/ 2023 - Present

Islamabad, Pakistan **Unity Game Developer**

Five River Solutions 09/2022 - 10/2023

Islamabad, Pakistan Jr.Unity Game Developer

3 Ace Studio 01/2022 - 08/2022

Bahawalpur, Punjab, Pakistan Jr.Unity Game Developer

JHU Technology 08/2021 - 12/2021

Islamabad, Pakistan

Jr.Unity Game Developer

JHU Technology 05/2021 - 07/2021

Bahawalpur, Punjab, Pakistan Internship Unity Game Developer

SKILS

- C#
- Game Design
- Problem Solving
- Analytics Integration
- Unity Game Development
- Communication Skills
- ADS Integration
- Game Planing